Herman & Conway Associates "Interpreting the Labor News" 5875
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Herman & Conway Associates "Interpreting the Labor News"
1949-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Herman & Conway Associates
5875
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5722894
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Herman & Conway Associates.
5722894
- July-December, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- January-June, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- July-December, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- January-June, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- July-December, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- January-June, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- January-July, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- July-December, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- January-June, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- July-December, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- January-December, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- January-June, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- January-June, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- March-December, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- January-December, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- January-December, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- January-December, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- January-December, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- July-December, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- January-June, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- June-December, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- January-October, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- January-June, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Executive's Report, September, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Executive's Report, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- General Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- January-April, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Executive's Reports, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- October-December, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- January-June, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- June-December, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Executive Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- January-June, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- January-June, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- July-December, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- July-December, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 17)